

PROFILE

Spirited and outspoken game developer, with 2+ years of experience, specialising on mobile.

With experience in designing and developing games from their conceptual phase, all the way into production.

Leading small teams (2-3 people) in creating fresh experiences meant to be played casually.

But ultimately, a man on a mission to create places of joy in life & work.

INFO

Country of Residence: Venezuela

Willing to Relocate: Yes

Phone No. +58 (412) 099 48 94

Email: jaykozatt@gmail.com

Portfolio: jaykozatt.github.io

Blog: jaykozatt.medium.com

JAY KOZATT

Gameplay Engineer / Designer

(Legal Name: Jonathan Reyes)

EXPERIENCE

Game Developer - Freelancer

MAY 2023 - PRESENT

- Recreated gameplay from scratch using video as reference.
- Created a system to endlessly generate random levels...
- Designed app icons for use in the Play Store.
- Matched and completed a walking animation in pixel art.
- Implemented fully functioning multiplayer, including lobby and matchmaking, for an existing mobile game.
- Worked on released titles:
 - o The Path
 - SumMatch

Unity Developer - Self-employed - Team Leader SEPTEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

- Organised a long-term project following agile methodologies.
- Established a relationship with renowned Noodlecake Studio for potential future release of our title "All Bets Are Off!" under their publishing umbrella.
- The main driving force behind most game design decisions.
- Designer and implementer of gameplay solutions.
- Both director and artist, involved in the art creation of our projects.
- Released titles:
 - All Bets Are Off!
 - o The Prisoner: Dread or Trust
 - o Gaia's Revenge (Prototype)

Unity Developer @ Studio Dread

MAY 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Programmer at budding indie studio under revshare model.
- Spearheaded a significant part of the initial organisation efforts of a team of 12 developers, and the core project structure.
- Assessed and reviewed game design decisions.
- In charge of implementing core game mechanics & systems.
- Co-lead the art direction of our projects.

EDUCATION

Computation Engineering @ Universidad Simón Bolívar Caracas, Venezuela 2012 - 2020

INFO

Country of Residence: Venezuela

Willing to Relocate: Yes

Phone No. +58 (412) 099 48 94

Email:

jaykozatt@gmail.com

Portfolio: jaykozatt.github.io

Blog: jaykozatt.medium.com

TECH PROFICIENCIES

Game Engines	Unity Engine RPG Maker VX Ace
Unity Development Tools	Ink - Narrative Scripting Lang. ProBuilder Cinemachine DOTween Shader Graph (URP) Netcode for GameObjects Lobby and Relay
Image Editing Software	Aseprite Illustrator Photoshop Paint.NET
Audio	FMOD Studio Audacity
Languages	C# Ruby Python HTML, CSS, Javascript
Database Managers	PostgreSQL SQLite 3